For every beginning there is an end.
Final Destination 2 is a horror, mystery film directed by David R. Ellis.
When Kimberly has a violent premonition of a highway pileup she blocks the
freeway, keeping a few others meant to die, safe...Or are they?
The survivors mysteriously start dying and it's up to
Kimberly to stop it before she's next.
Clear Rivers, played by Ali Larter.
Kimberly Corman, played by A. J. Cook.
Thomas Burke, played by Michael Landes.
Evan Lewis, played by David Paetkau.
Tim Carpenter, played by James Kirk.
Nora Carpenter, played by Lynda Boyd.
Final Destination 2 is a 2003 American supernatural
horror film directed by David R.
Ellis from a screenplay by J.
Mackye Gruber and Eric Bress, based on a story by
Gruber, Bress, and Jeffrey Reddick.
It is a sequel to Final Destination (2000) and the second
installment in the Final Destination film series.
The film stars Ali Larter, A.
Cook, and Michael Landes.
The film follows a young woman who saves a group of drivers from a
highway pile-up, which she predicted from a premonition.
She must find ways to defeat Death after the
survivors begin dying in freak accidents.
After the financial success of Final Destination, New Line Cinema
contacted Reddick regarding plans for a sequel.
Since the original film's crew was unavailable, New Line
replaced most of the production team.
Filming took place in Vancouver and Okanagan Lake.
Final Destination 2 was released on January 31, 2003.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
It grossed $46 million domestically and $43 million overseas, earning
$90 million internationally against a $26 million budget.
It was also nominated for four awards, including the
Saturn Award for Best Horror Film.
The highway scene was called the "greatest car crash scene in movie history" and
was nominated for the MTV Movie Award for Best Action Sequence.
A third film, Final Destination 3, was released in February 2006.
The film explores themes of ambulance, car crash, premonition, vision, hospital.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.